welcome everyone to the last jigsaw talk
欢迎大家参加最后的拼图游戏
of the day this is advanced modular
今天是先进的模块化
development my name is Alex Buckley I'm
我的名字叫亚历克斯·巴克利
in the Java platform group at Oracle I
在Oracle I的Java平台组中
do the first half of this talk and then
做这个演讲的前半部分，然后
my colleague Alan Bateman does the
我的同事艾伦·贝特曼（Alan Bateman）
second half mark is here for emotional
下半场是激动的时刻
support
支持
this is believe it or not even though
这是相信与否，即使
it's the end of the day this is the
这是一天的结束
third of five jigsaw talks Alan will
艾伦将进行的五次七巧板讲座中的三分之一
have the times dates and times of these
有这些时间的日期和时间
at the end of the presentation but
在演示的结尾，但是
modules and services and projects are
模块，服务和项目是
under the hood are tomorrow in this room
引擎盖下的是明天在这个房间里
and then we also start the repeats of
然后我们也开始重复
the whole cycle with prepare for JDK 9
为JDK 9做准备的整个周期
and I think that's on Wednesday that
我认为那是星期三
that's that's not getting repeated
那就是不再重复
tomorrow so anyway this talk is in two
明天，无论如何，这次谈话是在两个
parts and they're really both about
零件，它们实际上都是关于
migration because there are there's a
迁移，因为那里有一个
whole module system API you can look at
您可以查看整个模块系统API
the Javadoc for that but the the first
Javadoc，但第一个
and most existential question when
最存在的问题是什么时候
modularizing an application for jdk 9 is
模块化jdk 9的应用程序是
is where do the modules come from and
模块是从哪里来的？
that's really what this talk is about so
这才是真正的话题
I'm going to talk about migrating your
我要谈谈迁移您的
application top-down and then Alan will
应用程序自上而下，然后艾伦将
speak about migrating libraries that sit
谈论迁移坐的图书馆
closer to the JDK than your application
比您的应用程序更接近JDK
so that's bottom-up migration so
所以这是自下而上的迁移
application migration at heart a typical
从本质上讲，应用程序迁移
application has three layers at the top
应用程序在顶部有三层
are your jar files at the bottom is the
您的jar文件在底部是
JDK and in the middle of this sandwich
JDK和这个三明治的中间
is the filling a bunch of jars
是装满一罐子
downloaded from the internet in the
从互联网上下载的
nicest possible way and thrown on your
最好的方法，扔给你
class path in project jigsaw we've
项目拼图中的类路径
turned the JDK into modules such as Java
将JDK转换为Java之类的模块
base Java logging Java sequel and
基本Java日志记录Java续集和
or XML modules are good things they're
或XML模块是好东西
always in greetin their benefits are
总是问候他们的好处是
strong encapsulation so that no one
强大的封装，让没人
outside a module can access its
模块外部可以访问其
internals and reliable configuration so
内部和可靠的配置，因此
modules know what they need and there's
模块知道他们需要什么，
no need to set the class path if this
如果这不需要设置类路径
sounds good you might be wondering how
听起来不错，您可能想知道如何
to turn your application into modules
将您的应用程序变成模块
let's put some names on the jars at the
让我们在罐子上放一些名字
top to get started let's assume that the
首先，让我们假设
main application is my app jar and it
主要应用是我的应用jar
has some helper code in my Lib jar and
我的Lib jar中有一些帮助程序代码，
let's assume that the cloud of
让我们假设
third-party jars that filling in the
第三方罐子
sandwich can be simplified to just
三明治可以简化为
Jackson the JSON processing library
Jackson JSON处理库
Jackson comes as three jars core data
杰克逊来了三个罐子的核心数据
bind and annotations of course to run
绑定和注释当然要运行
the application today you have to ensure
今天的应用程序，您必须确保
the classpath is set up like this
类路径是这样设置的
everything's in the Lib directory I'm
一切都在我的Lib目录中
gonna have my things first and then the
首先要有我的东西，然后
Jackson jars and then my main class no
杰克逊罐子，然后是我的主班
problem JDK AIDS now you wouldn't have
问题JDK AIDS现在您不再需要
to bother with that long invocation that
长时间的打扰
sets the class path to this and that and
将类路径设置为此和
the other if my APR and my lib car
另一个是我的APR和我的lib车
turned into modules now turning each jar
变成模块，现在转动每个罐子
into a module one for one is a fairly
一对一地讲是相当公平的
natural way to proceed is not always
自然的前进方式并不总是
possible especially if jars have cyclic
可能尤其在罐子具有循环性的情况下
dependencies among their classes but
他们的班级之间的依赖关系
let's go with it for now whenever you
现在就让我们一起去吧
see a module you should ask two
看到一个模块，你应该问两个
questions what does it require and what
质疑它需要什么以及什么
does it exports let's ask that for each
它是否出口，让我们问每个
of our prospective modules my app and my
我们的预期模块我的应用程序和我的
Lib
解放
one way to find out what a module might
找出模块可能的一种方法
require is to run Jade EPS on the jar
要求是在罐子上运行Jade EPS
file that you have Jade EPS is a tool in
您拥有Jade EPS的文件是其中的工具
JDK 8 that analyzes classes in jar files
分析jar文件中的类的JDK 8
and finds whatever classes they refer to
并找到他们所引用的任何类
in other jar files here are the results
在其他jar文件中，这是结果
of running Jade EPS
Jade EPS的运行
on my jaw and my Libby are the classes
我的下巴和我的利比在上课
of my apt jar make use of classes in
我的apt jar使用了
jackson core and jackson data bind jar
杰克逊核心和杰克逊数据绑定罐
and of course in my live jar that's the
当然在我的活罐子里
helper plus my app dot jar uses classes
助手加上我的应用程序点罐使用类
from the java base module I'm pretty
从Java基本模块中我很漂亮
sure java.lang object is among them
确保java.lang对象在其中
since that's down in base and string as
因为这是在基础和字符串
an Ullman and for sake of argument it
厄尔曼人，为了论证它
uses Java sequel as well
也使用Java续集
my lib jar turns out to only use classes
我的lib jar只能使用类
from the java base module so that's nice
来自Java基本模块，所以很好
and simple the arrows are my app depends
和简单的箭头是我的应用程序取决于
on all sorts of things and my lib and
在各种各样的事情上，我的lib和
then my lib is just for sake of argument
那我的lib只是为了争辩
depending on on the JDK itself so with
取决于JDK本身，因此
this knowledge we can write the module
这些知识我们可以编写模块
declarations here's the module info Java
声明是模块信息Java
file from my Lib our helper library all
我的助手库中的所有文件
it requires is Java dot base now you
现在需要的是Java点库
never actually need to write Java base
从未真正需要编写Java基础
since it's literally impossible to write
因为实际上是不可能写的
a Java program without indirectly
没有间接的Java程序
relying on java.lang object so we always
依靠java.lang对象，所以我们总是
give you the dependency on Java base for
给你对Java基础的依赖
free even if you don't write it in
免费，即使您不写
source but put it out here to be clear
来源，但将其放在此处清楚
now there's an exports here which which
现在这里有出口
I've written by hand
我亲手写的
Jade EPS cannot realistically help you
Jade EPS无法切实帮助您
determine the exports of your jar we
确定您的罐子的出口，我们
could just say it exports everything but
可以说它出口了所有东西，
when you're writing the module
在编写模块时
declaration you still have to choose so
声明您仍然必须选择
let's say that my lib exports a package
假设我的lib导出了一个包
comm my apt Lib util to the my app
将我的apt Lib util通讯到我的应用
module we're going to make now this is a
现在我们要制作的模块是
qualified X
合格的X
but because it's specific about which
但是因为它具体说明了
other modules namely my app can access
其他模块，即我的应用程序可以访问
this exported package in particular the
这个导出的包，特别是
public types of that exported package
该导出包的公共类型
let's now turn to the module info dot
现在转到模块信息点
Java file for my app it requires my Lib
我的应用程序的Java文件需要我的Lib
our newly created module and it requires
我们新创建的模块，它需要
Java base and Java sequel and of course
Java基础和Java续集，当然
we know that it's going to use Jackson
我们知道它将使用杰克逊
so we'd like to write requires Jackson
所以我们要写要求杰克逊
core and requires Jackson data bind does
核心，并要求Jackson数据绑定
that mean that the I is the developer of
表示我是
my app have to write module info dot
我的应用程序必须编写模块信息点
Java files for Jackson as well that
杰克逊的Java文件
would be a pain I don't control those
我无法控制那些会很痛苦
jar files if only there was some way for
如果只有某种方式可以保存jar文件
the Jackson jar files to become modules
Jackson jar文件成为模块
automatically in that case we could then
在这种情况下，我们可以自动
write the Declaration of the my app
编写我的应用程序的声明
module module effort of Java like this
这样的Java模块的模块工作量
we just require those jars like any
我们只需要像那些罐子一样
other module we would have a beautiful
其他模块，我们将有一个美丽的
module growth with my app depending on
我的应用程序的模块增长取决于
my lib those are two explicit modules
我的库，这是两个显式模块
and my app depending on some of the
和我的应用，具体取决于
Jackson modules and then also down on
杰克逊模块，然后也下降
JDK modules you can do this
您可以执行JDK模块
the solution is automatic modules an
解决方案是自动模块
automatic module is a jar file that you
自动模块是您的jar文件
put on the module path rather than on
放在模块路径上，而不是放在
the class path once you do that you have
一旦完成，就可以上课
a real module you don't change someone
一个真正的模块，您无需更改任何人
else's jar file you don't put you don't
其他的jar文件，你不要放，你不要
change its manifest you don't put any
改变它的清单，你不要放任何
class files into it the name of that
类文件到它的名称
module is derived from the jar file name
模块是从jar文件名派生的
in a fairly obvious way it strips the
以相当明显的方式剥离
version off the end another thing
版本结束另一件事
that automatic module exports all of the
该自动模块会导出所有
packages there's like sure there's
包，就像肯定有
nothing else you can do really it
你别无他法
exports all the packages from the
从中导出所有软件包
automatic module and that automatic
自动模块和自动
module requires all other modules that
模块需要所有其他模块
are in the system
在系统中
so in effect automatic modules mean that
因此，实际上，自动模块意味着
today's jar files do running on JDK
今天的jar文件确实可以在JDK上运行
eight are tomorrow's modules they can
八个是明天可以使用的模块
act as modules in JDK 9 very often
经常在JDK 9中充当模块
without you doing anything without you
没有你就做什么
doing anything to them rather so once
一次对他们做任何事情
automatic modules spring into existence
自动模块应运而生
for jackson core jax and data bind and
用于杰克逊核心jax和数据绑定，以及
jackson annotations the module graph
杰克逊注释模块图
looks quite different
看起来很不一样
the automatic modules basically require
自动模块基本上需要
everything that's a feature not a bug
一切都是功能而不是错误
they require each other they require all
他们需要彼此，他们需要所有
the modules in the JDK image and all of
JDK映像中的模块以及所有
your modules that the errors are going
您的模块错误正在发生
up as well now this is to provide the
现在还可以提供
maximum possible that maximum possible
最大可能
compatibility surface for code in all
所有代码的兼容面
the jar files you might think that the
jar文件，您可能会认为
module system could run Jade EPS on the
模块系统可以在
the jar files those three jar files at
jar文件中的这三个jar文件
startup and try to figure out what
启动并尝试找出什么
modules they require but that wouldn't
他们需要的模块，但是不需要
really help and the reason it held we
真的有帮助，它使我们保持的原因
reason it wouldn't help is a bit subtle
它无济于事的原因有点微妙
the thing is that the libraries that you
事情是，你的图书馆
typically find in the filling of the
通常在填充
sandwich often make use of core
三明治经常利用芯
reflection that is the java.lang reflect
反射即java.lang反映
api and they use it to inspect classes
api，他们使用它来检查类
dynamically now Jade EPS can see the
动态，现在Jade EPS可以看到
invocations of the core reflection API
核心反射API的调用
but it can't can't very well predict
但它不能很好地预测
aesthetically what classes will be
从美学上讲，什么班级是
inspected dynamically and in fact the
动态检查，实际上
Jackson data bind module does exact
Jackson数据绑定模块确实正确
makes exactly this use of Cora flexion
正是利用了Cora屈曲
when code in my app here it is doing an
当我的应用程序中的代码在这里执行
import of the jackson api and then calls
导入杰克逊api，然后调用
the jackson api object mapper it passes
它通过的杰克逊api对象映射器
there it is the final argument it passes
那里是它传递的最后一个论点
it's own class object the intent is that
它是自己的类对象，目的是
Jackson data binds can create an
Jackson数据绑定可以创建一个
instance of the my value class which is
我的值类的实例是
an application class why so that it can
一个应用程序类为什么可以
then assign the field name to Bob and
然后将字段名称分配给Bob和
age to 13 because that's doing JSON
年龄为13岁，因为这是JSON
object mapping now on Jenna key nine
对象映射现在在珍娜键九上
this code won't succeed because we never
这段代码不会成功，因为我们从来没有
actually got round to saying what the
实际上是想说什么
module my app exports my app doesn't
模块我的应用程序导出我的应用程序不
really have an API it's the top node
真的有一个API，它是顶级节点
it's the application yet it needs to
这是应用程序，但需要
export some packages anyway and you may
无论如何导出一些包，您可能
find if you're using any frameworks at
查找您是否在使用任何框架
all
所有
even if you don't think as an
即使你不认为
application that you have an API that
您拥有一个API的应用程序
other people call you have this implicit
别人称你有这个隐性
API anyway you add it at inject right or
无论如何，您都可以在API右侧添加API或
at entity or at path per am or you pass
在实体上或在路径上，或者您通过
any of your own class objects down to a
您自己的任何类对象，直至
library the solution is to declare my
库的解决方案是声明我的
app as a weak module a week module
应用作为每周弱模块
exports all of its packages in a way
以某种方式导出其所有包装
that allows a framework like Jackson
允许像杰克逊这样的框架
data bind to reflect over its internals
数据绑定以反映其内部
you do not need to manually export the
您无需手动导出
packages one by one and then keep this
一个接一个地打包，然后保留这个
module declaration up-to-date with the
模块声明是最新的
source tree of my app with a weak module
具有弱模块的我的应用程序的源代码树
in effect you get the benefit of
实际上，您从中受益
reliable dependencies but without the
可靠的依赖关系，但没有
full strength or the full power of
的全部力量或全部力量
strong encapsulation frameworks that
强大的封装框架
reflect over application code are a
反映应用程序代码是
reality in everyday Java developments
日常Java开发中的现实
and they aren't going away so
他们并不会因此消失
application code like my app can't
像我的应用程序一样的应用程序代码
always be strongly encapsulated there is
总是被强烈封装
business value in the frameworks that
框架中的业务价值
call back in to you reflectively so we
反省地给您回电，以便我们
think this weak modifier at the very
认为这个弱修正
beginning of a module declaration is a
模块声明的开始是
clear statement about the nature of this
关于此性质的明确声明
module it's it's open for reflection but
它是开放的反思，但
it doesn't have an API
它没有API
without the weak modifier a module is
没有弱修饰符的模块
strong it explicitly defines an API via
它通过以下方式明确定义了API：
exports statements so let's come back to
导出语句，让我们回到
the module graph it is pretty messy but
模块图很杂乱，但是
it's better than when everything was a
比一切都还好
jar on the class path by the way because
罐子在类路径上的方式是因为
my app I should say because my app is
我应该说我的应用，因为我的应用是
now exporting what it needs to do that
现在导出它需要执行的操作
arrow that says data bind is gonna
表示数据绑定的箭头会
require implicitly my app there's that
隐式地要求我的应用程序是
and then there's the export from my app
然后从我的应用程序导出
because it's a week module and all the
因为这是一周的课程，
reflection from data bind will just work
数据绑定的反射将起作用
but the overall graph is still pretty
但是总体图还是不错的
messy but better than the class part
凌乱但比班级要好
because for example there is no arrow
因为例如没有箭头
from my lib to my app so there is no
从我的库到我的应用程序，所以没有
danger of code in my Lib accidentally
Lib中意外存在代码危险
reaching into my apps internals on the
深入了解我的应用内部
class path code in my live jar could
我的活动jar中的类路径代码可以
access code in my app jar quite easily
轻松访问我的应用程序罐中的代码
it's just in scan the class path until
它只是在扫描类路径，直到
you find the class and that kind of
你会发现课程和那种
chaos is what causes maintenance
混乱是导致维护的原因
headaches down the road in fact if you
实际上，如果您头痛，
think about it the class path at the end
想一想最后的课堂路径
please the class path is crazy with just
请上课之路
10 jars you get 100 possible ways for
10罐，您有100种可能的方式
classes in those jars to interact the
这些罐子中的类来交互
class path is the ultimate in airasia
班级路线是亚航的终极目标
whatever you know about the structure of
无论你知道什么结构
your system the class path throws it
您的系统的类路径将其抛出
away and connects everything to everyone
走开，将一切都连接到每个人
else and that means conflicting classes
否则，这意味着班级冲突
and missing classes and duplicate
和缺少类和重复
classes in different jars and generally
通常放在不同的罐子里
slow sequential look up every time the
每次缓慢进行顺序查找
VM needs a class which is often with
VM需要经常使用的类
modules you're telling the compiler and
您要告诉编译器的模块
VM about the structure of your system
VM关于您的系统结构
and automatic modules you know there is
和你知道的自动模块
a tension between the cleanliness and
清洁与
the usability but it all works out
可用性，但一切都可行
you're telling the compiler ovm about
您正在告诉编译器ovm关于
the structure of your system and finally
系统的结构，最后
they make use of that information
他们利用这些信息
speaking of the compiler let's see how
说到编译器，让我们看看
you run it for these module declarations
您为这些模块声明运行它
I've been talking about we've got the
我一直在谈论我们已经
Jax and jar files in the Lib directory
Lib目录中的Jax和jar文件
where they always were and we're going
他们一直在哪里，我们要去
to treat them at compile time as
在编译时将它们视为
automatic modules by putting them on the
自动模块，方法是将它们放在
module path to the compiler then we've
编译器的模块路径，然后
got the my app and my lip source in the
在我的应用程序和我的嘴唇来源
source directory and we tell Java C
源目录，我们告诉Java C
about that directory with this new
关于这个目录与这个新
module source path option and that's
模块源路径选项，那就是
necessary because there is a there's a
必要的，因为那里有一个
new level in the directory hierarchy for
目录层次结构中的新级别
the modules so we go you can see sort my
这些模块，让我们开始吧，您可以看到对我的排序
app and my lib are a new level in the
app和我的lib在
traditional compiled time hierarchy so
传统的编译时间层次结构
that we can put in source module name
我们可以输入源模块名称
and then module info dot Java and then
然后模块信息点Java，然后
the package hierarchy at the same level
同一级别的程序包层次结构
as module inferred on Java the result
作为在Java上推断结果的模块
then is class files minus D in the mods
然后是类文件减去mod中的D
directory we can run jar to build my
我们可以运行jar来建立我的目录
Libby are based on the classes in mods
Libby基于mod中的类
my lip we could run jar to build my app
我的嘴唇，我们可以运行罐子来建立我的应用程序
jar from the classes in mods my app and
从我的应用程序中的类的罐子里
because it's going to be the main class
因为它将成为主要课程
we specify that on the command line here
我们在命令行上指定
and then because these jar files have
然后因为这些jar文件
module info dot class files in them
其中的模块信息点类文件
compiled from the to module in photo
从照片中的to模块编译
java files we call them modular jars
我们称其为模块化jar的Java文件
modular jars is a term you will hear a
模块化罐子是一个术语，您会听到
lot in the the the succeeding talks in
在接下来的会谈中
this in this sequence so you can then
按此顺序进行操作，这样您就可以
run the module Erised application with
使用以下命令运行模块Erised应用程序
this simple command-line all the stuff
这个简单的命令行所有的东西
passed to minus CP in the past is now
过去传给负CP的现在
wrapped up in the module inferred or
包装在推断的模块中
class files the explicit modules are in
显式模块所在的类文件
Emily but I think I'm moving there from
艾米丽（Emily），但我想我正从那里搬到那里
mods and the automatic Jack's and
国防部和自动杰克和
modules are in Lib where they always
模块始终位于Lib中
were and so that's it
曾经就是这样
so we modular raised an application with
所以我们模块化提出了一个应用程序
two techniques first we built modular
首先我们建立了两种技术
jar files for our own application code
我们自己的应用程序代码的jar文件
by writing and compiling module in photo
通过在照片中编写和编译模块
Java files and we also created automatic
Java文件，我们还创建了自动文件
modules for third-party code for library
库的第三方代码模块
code simply by putting their jar files
只需将其jar文件放入代码
on the module path passing that Lib
在通过该Lib的模块路径上
directory to module path rather than to
目录到模块路径，而不是
class path so if you like you can think
上课的路径，所以如果您愿意可以考虑
of this as top-down migration I wrote
作为自上而下的迁移，我写道
the module declarations for the
的模块声明
application and then kind of worried
申请，然后有点担心
about what was underneath it later so if
关于它下面的内容，如果
I say top-down you should think what
我说自上而下你应该怎么想
does bottom-up migration look like and
自下而上的迁移看起来像和
for that I will hand over to Allen
为此，我将交给艾伦
library migration so this is the second
库迁移，这是第二次
part so we will roll back to where we
部分，所以我们将回滚到我们
were at the beginning of the
在开始时
presentation where we had the modular
介绍我们进行模块化的地方
platform at the bottom or sandwich of
平台在底部或三明治
jar files in the middle and our
中间和我们的jar文件
application whatever libraries it comes
应用程序附带的任何库
with at the top so what we're going to
与顶部，所以我们要去
do is we're going to start at the bottom
要做的是我们将从底部开始
now and try and move these de Jackson
现在尝试移动这些de Jackson
jar files that we have we want to move
我们要移动的jar文件
and migrate those two modules so that we
并迁移这两个模块，以便我们
end up with this picture green is module
最终得到这张照片绿色是模块
Maya I'm sorry orange is the is the
玛雅对不起，橙色是
class path exactly as Alex did in the
类路径与Alex在
first part of the presentation when
演示的第一部分
you're when you're migrating and you're
你在移民的时候
and you see a module you have to ask us
你看到一个模块，你必须问我们
the questions what do they require what
问题他们需要什么
did they say what are they export so for
他们是否说他们要出口什么
each of our three Jackson jar files if
我们三个杰克逊jar文件中的每个文件，如果
we're going to think of them as modules
我们将把它们视为模块
we need to think about what do they
我们需要考虑一下他们是做什么的
require and what did they export we
要求以及他们出口了什么
start with the report with the with by
从报表开始
running what we call the Jade EPS tool
运行我们所谓的Jade EPS工具
so if you're at the earlier talks you
因此，如果您在较早的演讲中
will see that we use the Jade EPS tune
会看到我们使用了Jade EPS音调
to actually do some static analysis on
实际上对
existing libraries alex sees it in his
亚历克斯现有的图书馆在他的书中看到了
part of the presentation to to look at
演示的一部分，以查看
Maya Pande my lip we do the same thing
Maya Pande我的嘴唇，我们也做同样的事情
with the Jackson jar files here to
与杰克逊罐子文件在这里
understand what they require so we see
了解他们的需求，所以我们看到
that the Jackson annotations and jar
杰克逊的注解和罐子
file has code in there that makes use of
文件中包含可以利用的代码
types that are in Java base that makes
以Java为基础的类型
sense java jackson core also has some
感觉java杰克逊核心也有一些
code in there that makes use of some
那里的代码利用了一些
types in Java base jackson data bind is
Java基本杰克逊数据绑定中的类型是
much more interesting there is code in
更有趣的是，其中有代码
that jar file that has references to
具有引用的jar文件
types that are injects and annotations
注入和注释的类型
there's also references that types that
也有引用类型
hurt in in jackson core there's also a
在杰克逊核心受伤，还有一个
couple of other references to two types
其他两种对两种类型的引用
that are in java base of course java
在java基础上当然是java
sequel and java x xml
续集和Java X XML
I should say is is that when you're when
我应该说的是，当你在
you're trying to understand what a
您正在尝试了解什么
module depends on you don't need to of
模块取决于您不需要的
course use the the J tips - there's all
当然使用J技巧-全部
the ways if it's a maven project than
如果这是一个Maven项目，
you've already got a palm and that could
你已经有了手掌，那可以
give you some idea what what it depends
让您知道它的含义
on
上
so this is the dependency graph from
所以这是来自
from the J tips output and just keep
从J技巧输出中，并保持
just keep this in mind because we will
请记住这一点，因为我们会
be coming back to us in the later slides
在后面的幻灯片中回到我们身边
and I want to run J tips again this time
而且这次我想再次运行J技巧
with a new option gen module info which
带有新的选项生成模块信息
is a way basically to get your starting
基本上是一种开始的方式
point on your starting module info dot
指向您的起始模块信息点
Java now in the earlier talks we had J
现在，在Java的早期讨论中，我们有了J
Depp's being usable on JDK 8 to be able
Depp可在JDK 8上使用
to look at your jar files in your
看你的jar文件
applications as using with jdk age and
与jdk age和
older
年长的
the diversion of j tips that's in jdk 9
jdk 9中j技巧的转移
has a bunch of additional options that
还有很多其他选择
that aren't available in the eighth
第八种没有的
version and this is one of the
版本，这是其中之一
command-line options that is that is new
这是新的命令行选项
in the jdk 9 version when you run j
在jdk 9版本中运行j
depp's
德普的
on on a bunch of jar files with the gen
与一堆jar文件一起
module info it will generate you a
模块信息，它将为您生成
starting Java info sorry module info so
启动Java信息对不起模块信息所以
I've run it on these three jar files and
我已经在这三个jar文件上运行了
it has created me 3 module info sworn
它给我创造了3个模块信息
for each of the jar files and we look at
对于每个jar文件，我们来看
that in the next slide so for Jackson
在下一张幻灯片中，对于杰克逊
data by which is probably the most
可能是最多的数据
interesting one in this set of jar files
这组jar文件中有趣的一个
this is the module info that the J tips
这是J提示的模块信息
tool created for me does a bunch of
为我创建的工具做了很多
requires at the top that that is based
要求在顶部
on the static analysis of what's in the
对其中的内容进行静态分析
jar file and J depths has no idea which
jar文件和J depths不知道哪个
which which M parts of the jar file are
jar文件的哪M个部分是
in the exported API and which are
在导出的API中，哪些是
internal so it assumes that every type
内部的，因此它假定每种类型
is part of the API therefore every
是API的一部分，因此每个
package is exported so it generates a
包被导出，因此它生成一个
little exports director for error for
小出口总监的错误
every one of the
每一个
the packages in the jar file if you look
如果您看，jar文件中的软件包
closely at the requires it also looks at
密切关注需求，同时也关注
the signature of the methods that are
这些方法的签名
and that's able to determine whether to
这样就可以确定是否
you whether to generator requires or
您是否需要发电机或
requires transitive so in the previous
需要传递，因此在前面
talk we talked about improve requires
我们谈论的谈话需要改进
transitive and so here you're seeing an
可传递的，所以在这里您看到
example of it in a generation module
在生成模块中的示例
info for this part of the talk assume
讨论的这一部分的信息假定
that we are the maintainer z' of this
我们是这个的维护者
library so we have much more knowledge
图书馆，所以我们有更多的知识
about this library than then then J tips
关于这个库，然后比J提示
does so and and as as maintainer z' of
这样做并作为维护者的z'
this library one of the things we will
这个图书馆，我们要做的一件事
want to do is are not want to do is we
想做的就是不想做的是我们
don't want to be exporting our input
不想导出我们的输入
packages that's where our turn olympian
包，这就是我们成为奥运选手的地方
implementation is it's not part of the
实施不是它的一部分
API and for this library we'll assume so
API，对于这个库，我们假设
what I might do is I might edit this
我可能会做的是编辑此内容
this generation module info and delete
此生成模块信息并删除
the exports that don't make sense so J
出口没有意义，所以J
tips generates me a module info that
提示会为我生成一个模块信息
where everything is declared as being
一切都被宣布为
exported but assume that as maintain
导出但假定为维持
errs that we know better and these
我们更了解的错误，这些
simple packages don't make sense so we
简单的包装没有意义，所以我们
will delete these as part of creating
将删除这些作为创建的一部分
the right module descriptor right margin
正确的模块描述符右边距
declaration for this Jackson data bind
此Jackson数据绑定的声明
module now we do the similar to what
模块现在我们做的类似于
Alex did and will start to compile this
亚历克斯做到了，并将开始对此进行编译
so what I've done is I've generated
所以我要做的就是生成
these module info into the source tree
这些模块信息进入源代码树
for these three modules that I'm going
我要去的这三个模块
to compile remember with with our our
与我们一起编译记忆
modules we have an additional directory
模块，我们有一个附加目录
now in the in the file path that is the
现在在文件路径中
module name so all my source code for
模块名称，因此我的所有源代码
these three modules is organized SRC
这三个模块是有组织的SRC
slash module name and then my
斜杠模块名称，然后是我的
traditional hierarchy of classes and
传统的阶级阶层和
organized by package in that tree my
在那棵树上按包裹组织
module info is in the top-level
模块信息在顶层
directory of each one of the modules so
每个模块的目录，因此
for Jackson core the location of the
对于杰克逊核心的位置
module info is SRC slash module named
模块信息是名为SRC的斜杠模块
Jackson core slash module info Java
Jackson核心斜线模块信息Java
same for the other three the other two
其他三个相同
modules
模组
I'm now going to compile all of these
我现在要编译所有这些
three modules together so I'm
三个模块在一起，所以我
recompiling all of Jackson in this case
在这种情况下重新编译所有Jackson
all three of them and I'm do the multi
他们三个都在做
module compilation so what one Java C
模块编译是什么，一个Java C
command I'm compiling and all three
我正在编译的命令和所有三个
modules together I'm giving it the D an
模块在一起，我给它一个
output directory of mods that's where
mods的输出目录
all the class files are going to be
所有的类文件都将是
generated and the input to it I'm just
生成的和它的输入，我只是
giving it a fine command where to find
给它一个很好的命令在哪里找到
all of the the Java source so that will
所有的Java源代码，这样
that will compile I've now got a Mazda
将会编译，我现在有一个马自达
rectory with three directories in it and
带有三个目录的目录
all of the class files I'm going to run
我要运行的所有类文件
the jar command three times and because
jar命令3次，因为
I'm going to create a jar file for each
我将为每个创建一个jar文件
one of my modules this is these are
我的模块之一是
these are modular jars the options
这些是模块化的罐子
you're seeing on here is the isdon't is
你在这里看到的是不是
his new options in jdk 9 so and the jar
他在jdk 9 so和jar中的新选项
tool has historically and had very
该工具历史悠久，
obscure and very uniquely Java
晦涩难懂的Java
options and bit like the the zip tool
选项和有点像zip工具
some of them they be modernized and in
其中一些是现代化的
JDK 9 and particularly to use the canoe
JDK 9特别是使用独木舟
style format at least close to it as you
样式格式至少与您接近
saw that and maybe in the introduction
看到了，也许在介绍中
talked earlier on with some of the other
之前和其他人谈过
tools so the jar tool has - - options so
工具，因此jar工具具有--选项，因此
- - creation - - file so i'm creating a
--创建--文件，因此我正在创建
jar file i'm telling what jar file to
我要告诉的jar文件是什么
creation this is a modular jar and going
创建这是一个模块化的罐子
to creation in the envelope directory
在信封目录中创建
I'm naming it Jackson core and a version
我将其命名为Jackson核心和一个版本
number and telling it the dirt the
数字，并告诉它的污垢
location of the class files I'm going to
我要去的课程文件的位置
package in and I'm creating three
打包进去，我要创建三个
modular jars so that's really really
模块化的罐子，所以真的
nice exactly as Alex did with my app and
就像Alex对我的应用所做的一样，
my lid in the first part of the
我的盖子在第一部分
presentation now this is what we've got
现在的演示文稿，这就是我们所拥有的
now
现在
so we've recompiled Jackson core Jackson
所以我们重新编译了Jackson的核心Jackson
annotations and JAXA data bind we've
批注和JAXA数据绑定
packaged them up as modular jars this is
包装成模块化的罐子，这是
the module graph that we have some the
我们有一些模块图
platform modules at the bottom and then
底部的平台模块，然后
our three Jackson modules as explicit
我们的三个Jackson模块是明确的
modules their dependencies are clear
模块的依赖关系很明确
they're exports are clear this is a nice
他们很清楚这是一个很好的出口
module graph
模块图
just a recap for how we ran these on the
只是我们如何在这些上运行这些的回顾
classpath right at the beginning of the
类路径就在
presentation we're now going to change
我们现在要更改的演示文稿
this command so that we're running with
该命令，以便我们与
these these three libraries as modules
这三个库作为模块
so that's the old command now we've got
所以这是旧命令，现在我们有了
the new command so there if for those
新命令，如果有的话
that attended the intro talked earlier
参加介绍的人之前谈到
on I talked about how to mix the module
在上面我谈到了如何混合模块
path and the class path together this is
路径和类路径一起是
exactly a scenario where you have to do
正是您必须要做的一个场景
this because my app and my lib are on
这是因为我的应用程序和我的lib已打开
the class path r3 Jackson libraries are
类路径r3 Jackson库是
now modules on the module path so this
现在模块在模块路径上，所以这
both a module path and a class path
既是模块路径又是类路径
specified to the Java command here my
在这里指定给Java命令my
three Jackson modules are in the MU Lib
MU库中有三个Jackson模块
directory and I'm specify the EM Lib
目录，然后指定EM Lib
directory to the module path option my
目录到模块路径选项my
class path has been has Maya and my Lib
上课的路已经有了Maya和我的Lib
so I'm specifying those with this - CP
所以我要指定这些-CP
or - class path but exactly like the the
或-类路径，但与
intro talked earlier on there is nothing
之前介绍过的介绍没什么
to say in in Maya or my lib to say that
在Maya或我的lib中说
they depend on Jackson data bind
他们依赖杰克逊数据绑定
there's no dependency information
没有依赖项信息
available on the class path so I'm
在课程路径上可用，所以我
having to help the wrong time with the
不得不帮助错误的时间
add modules our option to tell it to
添加模块，我们可以选择告诉它
resolve the Jackson data buying module
解决Jackson数据购买模块
this is one of the complications when
这是当
you're trying to mix the the class path
您正在尝试混合类路径
and the module path together there's
和模块路径在一起
nothing on the class path to tell you
上课路上没有什么可以告诉你的
what in it what the dependencies are so
它里面有什么依赖性
I'm helping the runtime with the add
我正在通过添加帮助运行时
modules option to tell it I was all V
模块选项告诉我我都是V
the Jackson data bind so that is a
杰克逊数据绑定，所以这是一个
command line that I've ended up with
我最终得到的命令行
with modules on the module path and my
与模块路径和我的模块
application on the class path questions
上课路径问题的应用
at the end right so now we're going to
在最后，所以现在我们要
put it all together so I've got modules
放在一起，所以我有模块
on the bottom I'm going to take the
在底部，我将采取
modules that Alex generated in the first
Alex在第一个生成的模块
part of the talk and I'm going to
谈话的一部分，我要去
combine everything together this is what
结合一切，这就是
we have for the second
我们有第二个
TAF now we've got Alex's modules with my
TAF现在我们有了Alex的模块
app and my lip and we have this nice
应用程序和我的嘴唇，我们有这个好
module graph everything is green
模块图一切都是绿色的
everything is modules it's very very
一切都是模块，这非常非常
clear what the dependencies are in this
清除其中的依赖项
graph so now let's go and run this now
图，现在让我们开始运行它
that we have everything as modules
我们把一切都作为模块
just to recap everything is modules so
只是回顾一下一切都是模块，所以
if I look in my M Lib directory I have
如果我在我的M Lib目录中查找
five modular jars my app my Lib and my
我的应用程序，我的Lib和我的五个模块化罐子
three Jackson and modules my command to
三个杰克逊和我的命令模块
run this has shrunk because I'm just
运行它缩小了，因为我只是
telling it the module path and the
告诉它模块路径和
initial module then the initial module
初始模块，然后初始模块
our main module is my app so I'm going
我们的主要模块是我的应用程序，所以我要去
to ask it to run the to run my app that
要求它运行来运行我的应用
will resolve what does my app depend on
将解决我的应用程序依赖什么
life depends on on my lab depends on
生活取决于我的实验室
Jackson data byte we will generate the
杰克逊数据字节我们将生成
transitive closure all of these modules
所有这些模块的传递闭包
will get loaded in order to run and my
将被加载以便运行，我的
app we can go further so if we combine
应用程序，我们可以走得更远，所以如果我们结合起来
in the intro talk we had some simple
在介绍性谈话中，我们做了一些简单的
options are some simple examples using J
选项是使用J的一些简单示例
link to create runtime images now we
链接以创建运行时映像，现在我们
have our application and the Jackson
有我们的应用程序和杰克逊
libraries as modules we can actually do
库实际上是我们可以做的模块
the same kind of thing this is the
同样的事情是
advanced talk so I have a couple of
高级谈话，所以我有几个
Advanced Options on the J link option so
J链接选项上的高级选项，因此
what I'm producing here is a runtime
我在这里产生的是运行时
image that will have my app and all of
将会包含我的应用和所有
its transitive dependencies in a runtime
在运行时中的传递依赖
image so this is this is something that
图片，所以这就是
can be distributed with just the mount
可以与坐骑一起分发
modules that it needs so the options are
它需要的模块，所以选项是
giving two to J link just like Java C
给两个J链接，就像Java C
just like the Java launcher and giving
就像Java启动器一样
it the module path as to where to find
关于在哪里找到的模块路径
the modules I'm using the the add
我正在使用添加的模块
modules option telling J link what
模块选项告诉J链接
modules I'd like in the runtime image J
我在运行时映像J中想要的模块
link will generate the transitive
链接将生成可传递的
closure and link all of those modules to
关闭所有这些模块并将其链接到
create the runtime image
创建运行时映像
I want a relatively small image so I'm
我想要一个相对较小的图像，所以我
giving some options to do compression to
提供一些压缩选项
do some stripping there's like any
做一些剥离像
linker there's much more complicated
链接器要复杂得多
options I could give it to to do other
我可以给它做其他事情的选择
customizations of the run time image but
自定义运行时映像，但是
I'm just sticking with the size for now
我现在只是坚持大小
and what I ended up with is a run time
我最终得到的是运行时间
image that's hat that is in this case
在这种情况下是帽子的图像
it's twenty six thousand yeah so just
是2.66万，所以
about twenty five and a half megabytes
大约25个半兆字节
if I look in the bin directory I see in
如果我在bin目录中看到
there only a small set of tools and the
那里只有一小部分工具，
Java launcher I've CCC's something for
Java启动器我已将CCC用于
my app that has been generated by the
我的应用已由
linker if I run the list mod the lists
链接器，如果我运行列表mod列表
are list modules option on this
是列表模块选项
generated runtime then we see that it
生成的运行时，那么我们看到它
has this is the list of the modules that
有这是模块的列表
are in that runtime image my app and my
在该运行时映像中，我的应用程序和我的
Lib the Jackson libraries and then in
打开Jackson图书馆，然后进入
this case there's four platform modules
这个案例有四个平台模块
that have been M linked in so this is
被M链接的，所以这是
quite nice either I've ended up with a
非常好，要么我最终得到了
small runtime that for my application
适用于我的应用程序的运行时间短
and I can just run it with this there's
我可以用它来运行它
no module pack specified because they're
未指定模块包，因为它们是
all linked into the runtime image I can
我都可以链接到运行时映像中
just do Java - M my app and my
只是做Java-我的应用和我的
application will will will run in
应用程序将在
addition the linker will generate a
此外，链接器将生成一个
little launcher script for my
我的小启动脚本
application as well based on the module
基于模块的应用程序
name and so I can make the command line
名字，所以我可以做命令行
even shorter if I wish and that is a
如果我愿意，甚至更短，那是一个
quick run-through of things from the
快速浏览事物
bottom up and then combining the modules
自下而上，然后组合模块
that were generated from top down and so
是由上而下产生的
that everything is modules and then we
一切都是模块，然后我们
go further and actually create a custom
走得更远，实际上创建一个自定义
runtime image so the main thing we've
运行时映像，所以我们要做的主要事情
got through in this presentation is I
在这次演讲中获得成功的是我
hope that we've actually demonstrated is
希望我们实际展示的是
that you have the freedom to adopt and
您可以自由采用
migrate to modules at your own pace alex
以自己的步调迁移到模块alex
has shown how to how to migrate and
已经展示了如何迁移以及
marginalize applications before the
在申请之前将申请边缘化
libraries have had been migrated it's
图书馆已经迁移了
possible as we saw in the second half of
正如我们在下半年看到的那样
the presentation to marginalize
边缘化的演示
libraries completely independently
图书馆完全独立
in addition you've got a flavor for the
此外，您还对
different kinds of modules so um Alex
因此，不同种类的模块
started off with explicit modules for my
从我的显式模块开始
up and my lib and then made use of the
和我的lib，然后利用
Jackson libraries as automatic modules
杰克逊图书馆作为自动模块
that gives you a flavor of explicit
给你一种明显的感觉
versus automatic modules and also and
与自动模块以及
showed you what the current proposals on
向您展示了当前的建议
the table which is weak modules and how
哪个表是弱模块以及如何
that they can be actually used as well
他们也可以实际使用
for especially for applications that
特别适用于
don't export any in the api's so
不要在api中导出任何内容
hopefully that is giving you a flavor of
希望那能给你一种味道
what of what's there just to support and
什么只是支持和
migration to modules so we'll just
迁移到模块，所以我们只是
finish up with a nice catch line and go
以一条不错的接球线结束并走
forth and modulized so we have a couple
并经过调制，所以我们有几个
of other sessions and we're mostly in
其他会议，我们大部分时间都在
this room so we did with this is our
这个房间，所以我们这样做是我们的
third one today and we starting to
今天第三，我们开始
repeat this tomorrow at 2:30 and but the
明天2:30重复此步骤，但是
important talks that haven't been done
尚未完成的重要对话
yet are the modules and services at
尚未提供模块和服务
11:00 tomorrow and then alex is going to
明天11:00，然后亚历克斯要去
do project chick saw under the hood at
做项目在引擎盖下的小鸡锯
4:00 p.m. tomorrow and there's also a
明天下午4:00，还有一个
hack session which is then I think bring
hack session，我认为这带来了
along questions bring along your laptop
带着问题带上笔记本电脑
if you want to try things out that's on
如果你想尝试一下
Wednesday at 8:30 one of the rooms here
星期三8:30这里的其中一个房间
I'm not sure exactly sure which and
我不确定是哪个
that's the two are and more information
这就是两个，更多信息
so this is the link to the project
所以这是项目的链接
jigsaw page we're working on the
我们正在研究的拼图页面
implementation of project jigsaw there's
实施项目拼图
also a link to them there the mailing
也是他们那里邮件的链接
list and where the early access bills
清单以及提早使用帐单的位置
and let's see so as I said in the
就像我在
earlier talks earlier on is JDK 9 still
JDK 9仍然是早期的讨论
in development and it doesn't ship and
在开发中，它不发货，
it's not scheduled to ship until next
不会等到下一个
year so many of the things that were
一年中有很多事情
actually showing here are things that
实际上在这里显示的东西
are just not finally yet nothing is
只是最后还没有，什么都没有
final yet they're still just ours is
最后，但他们仍然只是我们的
still discussion they're still early
还在讨论他们还很早
access everything is is is still in
访问一切仍在
progress so what we've shown here may be
进步，所以我们在这里显示的可能是
the final JDK 9 isn't exactly like that
最终的JDK 9并非完全一样
so I think we're we've got about ten
所以我想我们大约有十个
minutes for questions if not
分钟，如果没有问题
we go 15 minutes if if people have
如果有人有，我们走15分钟
questions so protocol for questions will
问题，所以协议将
be if you can make it as far as the
如果你能做到的
front then call into the microphone so
然后打电话给麦克风
that people can hear otherwise we'll
人们会听到否则我们会
have to repeat the the questions so Marc
必须重复这些问题，所以马克
is available for questions as well we
也可以提出问题
can't actually hear when wouldn't yeah
真的听不到什么时候不会
yeah
是的
in the first one with the automatic
在第一个与自动
module Jackson automatically depended on
模块Jackson自动依赖
the my app which allowed it to do the
我的允许它执行的应用
reflection in the second one how does
在第二个反思如何
Jackson rely or reference this is a good
杰克逊依靠或参考这是一个很好的
question so the question is I was
问题，所以问题是我当时
wondering if someone would spot this in
想知道是否有人会发现这个
the first parts when Jax and data bind
Jax和数据绑定的第一部分
is an automatic module list it's
是一个自动模块列表
requiring implicitly actually Maya and
实际上隐式要求Maya和
my lib because it requires everything
我的lib，因为它需要一切
but then when Allen modularized it's
但是当艾伦模块化时
altogether the arrows are all down yes
箭头全都向下了
so so the thing is so data bind is using
所以事情就是这样，数据绑定正在使用
core reflection to access the classes
访问类的核心思考
the exported classes from my app my app
从我的应用程序导出的类
passes a class object to data binds that
将类对象传递给数据绑定
was in the little eight the person the
在八岁那年
data bind API and that means the code
数据绑定API，这意味着代码
and data binds can access all as almost
数据绑定几乎可以访问所有对象
a class as X that class is exported from
从X导出该类的类
my app data bind can reflect over it it
我的应用程序数据绑定可以反映出来
doesn't need it it actually gets an
不需要它实际上得到了
arrow for free going back up to my app
免费箭头返回到我的应用程序
even even even when data bind is an
即使数据绑定是
explicit module with the module
显式模块与模块
declaration but clearly it doesn't know
声明，但显然它不知道
what modules it will be what classes in
什么模块将是什么类
what modules it will be reflecting over
它将反映哪些模块
so it can't possibly say requires them
所以不可能说需要他们
when it reflects over them as long as
只要它反映在他们身上
the class is exported to it's the
该类被导出到
reflection just works which if you're
反射就可以了，如果你
paying very close attention is a change
密切关注是一个改变
from last year but pretend I didn't say
从去年开始，但假装我没有说
that it just works
它只是有效
Lincoln clearly means in effect he said
林肯显然意味着他说
to upgrade one of the jars
升级其中一个罐子
do I need to start from scratch for the
我需要从头开始吗
chair or for that module to rebuild
椅子或用于该模块的重建
image how the main is the version of
图片主要的版本
groups of individuals right so I think
一群人对，所以我认为
what you're asking is you need to rerun
您要问的是您需要重新运行
the late the the j-link command yeah
j-link命令的后期
yeah exactly
是啊
and J link will actually record the all
和J链接实际上将记录所有
the options that are actually used to
实际使用的选项
make it easy to rerun uh so if you have
可以很容易地重新运行呃，如果有的话
a new versions of the modules
模块的新版本
I was wondering if you could quickly go
我想知道你能不能快点走
over again what required transitive
再次需要什么传递
exposes about didn't say okay so this is
暴露关于没有说好，所以这是
so the question is about what what's
所以问题是什么
different about requires transitive
不同之处在于需要传递
versus requires java logging the full
与要求Java记录完整
answer is in jigsaw under the hood but
答案是在幕后的拼图中，但是
it's it's not a complicated feature it's
这不是一个复杂的功能
not an advanced feature so fair question
不是高级功能，如此公平的问题
so you'll see Jackson data bind requires
所以您会看到Jackson数据绑定要求
java logging it's an emoji is an
java记录它是一个表情符号是一个
implementation detail of data bind it's
数据绑定的实现细节
just it's just calling Logging's methods
只是调用Logging的方法
it's not exposing it in any way the data
它不会以任何方式公开数据
bind requires transitive Java XML now I
绑定现在需要传递Java XML
haven't looked at the data bind Java doc
没看过数据绑定Java doc
in detail but what the requires
详细，但需要什么
transitive java xml tells me is that the
传递Java xml告诉我的是
way that data bind depends on java xml
数据绑定的方式取决于java xml
isn't for just an implementation purpose
不只是为了实现目的
it's because the api of jackson data
这是因为杰克逊数据的api
bind somewhere in all these exports has
绑定所有这些出口中的某处
in a public signature a type from java
在公共签名中来自Java的类型
xml yes what do i write so if you write
xml是的，我怎么写，所以如果你写
a module that requires checks and data
需要检查和数据的模块
binds the fact that data bind says I
绑定数据绑定说我
depend transitivity on XML means your
依赖于XML的可传递性意味着您的
module you could say requires Java XML
您可以说需要Java XML的模块
is nothing wrong with that if you don't
如果你不这样做，那是没有错的
it will be as if you had said requires
就像您说过的要求
java xml what do you get from java xml
java xml你从java xml得到什么
whatever it exports everything it's how
无论出口什么，它都是如何
you get module leveled modular
您将获得模块级别的模块化
granularity dependencies while still
粒度依赖性
allowing refactoring by the way there's
允许通过以下方式进行重构
a couple of slides on this and the the
与此有关的几张幻灯片
intro talked from earlier you may have
之前介绍过的介绍，您可能有
missed that but it's you want to catch
错过了，但是你想抓住
up
上
two questions one one is save got three
两个问题，一个一保存，三个
third-party libraries and they were all
第三方库，它们都是
built with slightly different versions
内置略有不同的版本
of Jackson
杰克逊
3/3 okay sure or maybe okay so different
3/3好的，也许如此，如此不同
parts of your application maybe even yes
您的应用程序的某些部分甚至可以
using different versions of Jackson
使用不同版本的杰克逊
they're compatible they're just slightly
他们是兼容的，他们只是略
different bug fixes pick one does that
不同的错误修复程序可以做到这一点
mean everything else will still let me
意味着其他一切仍然会让我
ask the first let me ask another
问第一个让我问另一个
question your application Tran them it's
质疑您的应用程序
not your code necessarily the
不一定是您的代码
transitively uses different versions of
传递使用不同版本的
Jackson yeah how do you put those jars
杰克逊是的，你怎么放那些罐子
on the classpath enjoy decades but if
在课堂上享受数十年，但如果
you specify version one of some
您指定一些版本之一
third-party jar and later on on the
第三方jar，稍后
classpath version two of then we're done
然后我们完成了classpath版本2
if you just so you don't in in what
如果你只是这样，那么你不在
whatever you used to put on the
不管你以前穿什么
classpath you were now the exact same
你现在是完全相同的classpath
jar that you picked to put on the
您选择放入的罐子
classpath just put it on the module path
classpath只是将其放在模块路径上
yeah and then it magically I mean really
是的，然后神奇的是我的意思是真的
it's magic just becomes an automatic
魔术变成自动
module with the name and we drop the
具有名称的模块，然后删除
version qualifier according to some
根据一些版本限定符
heuristic that's in the Javadoc so these
启发式在Javadoc中是这样的
are these are the real module names I
这些是真实的模块名称吗
can get from that from the real jars the
可以从真正的罐子中得到
maven mr. main she kind you is behind
梅文先生她主要是你在后面
you and has an entire talk about that
你，并有一个完整的谈论
once you've upgraded an existing library
升级现有库后
system is it still possible to compile
系统仍然可以编译
it using the class path rather than the
它使用类路径而不是
new module so if you so so let's bring
新模块，如果您愿意，让我们带来
the applicant let's bring it up let's
申请人让我们提出来
bring the Java C in vacation right so
将Java C带入假期吧
here we are
我们来了
recompiling the library for jdk 9 right
为jdk 9重新编译该库
so this is the source that this is this
所以这就是这个的来源
is the library source I'm gonna compile
是我要编译的库资源
it put it into the mods directory the
它将其放入mods目录中
class files that come out of this will
由此产生的类文件将
be version 53 class files Java SE 9
是版本53的类文件Java SE 9
class files clearly they won't run
类文件显然不会运行
earlier than gdk9 what you can do right
早于gdk9您可以做什么
so so what you can so what you can do is
所以你可以做的是
compile the source once with - release
使用-release一次编译源代码
seven for example and then compile again
例如七个，然后再次编译
just the module in futur Java file files
只是未来Java文件文件中的模块
in this case don't specify - release the
在这种情况下，请不要指定-释放
default will be nine so that will that
默认值为9，这样
will give you class files where module
将为您提供类文件，其中模块
in for class is version 53 which has to
在课堂上是版本53，必须
be the rest of the classes from from
是来自的其余课程
these three source trees will be 51
这三个源树将是51
run them through jar the resulting files
通过jar运行它们生成的文件
will run on ya if if you're running
如果您正在跑步，它将在ya上运行
jetty q9 the that the class path will
码头q9班级路径将
still take modular jars just nothing
还是拿模块化的罐子
will read the module in footer class
将在页脚类中读取模块
files right with all with all of the
文件与所有
dependent with the N factorial
依赖于N阶乘
dependencies just to clarify what Alex
依赖关系只是为了澄清亚历克斯
it is is you can take a larger jar you
这是你可以拿一个更大的罐子
can put it on the class path and it'll
可以将其放在课程路径上
just work as a library in the class path
只是作为类路径中的库
as as it would have always done yeah I
一如既往，是的，我
would in the nicest possible way
会以最好的方式
question why you want to do that if
问题，为什么要这样做
you've made if you're running on jelly
如果已经在果冻上跑了
canine and you've made a module you
狗，你已经做了一个模块
written module for Java or you
Java或您的书面模块
found one why you would then want to put
找到了一个为什么要放的原因
it on the classpath on a on a JDK
它在JDK上的classpath上
installation clearly on a JDK 9
在JDK 9上清楚地安装
installation I'm trying to work out what
安装我试图找出什么
you're trying to do in time though I
你虽然想及时做
think you would expect the tools will
认为您会期望工具会
eventually had support for modules yes
最终获得了对模块的支持
start with the follow-up to his which is
从他的后续行动开始
it appears that if you put a module on a
看来，如果您将模块放在
regular class but in JDK 9 you are
普通班，但在JDK 9中
actually breaking the protections the
实际上打破了保护
access protections yes so yeah so the
访问保护是的，是的，所以
access protections are actually not as
访问保护实际上不是
tight as they may appear otherwise on
紧，否则可能会出现
the class path there is no such thing as
课堂上没有这样的东西
a modular jar on the class path they're
他们在课程路径上的模块化jar
just jars and because they're not
只是罐子，因为它们不是
modular jars we're ignoring modular
模块化罐子，我们忽略了模块化
fertile class we're ignoring the exports
富裕阶层我们忽略了出口
so there's no way for a publisher to
因此，发布商无法
kind of begin the protection into it's
开始保护它
only protecting the really the runtime
只保护真正的运行时
as as you configure it but the publisher
按照您的配置，但发布者
cannot they actually protect that's
他们真的不能保护那是
correct
正确
no that's true and and if you're in
不，那是真的，如果你在
control of the on disk layouts the on
控制磁盘上的布局
displacement of jar files you you are in
您所在的jar文件的置换
control of everything even if the
控制一切，即使
modular jar files are put on the module
模块化的jar文件放在模块上
path if you're controlling the command
路径（如果您正在控制命令）
leaf or controlling the environment you
离开或控制环境
can just say - - at exports and decides
只能说--在出口并决定
that you wish to as the the system
您希望作为系统
configurator overrule the exports in the
配置程序否决了
modular jars okay you can do that a new
模块化的罐子好吧，你可以做一个新的
first example legacy Charles if I wanted
如果我愿意，第一个示例是传统的Charles
to protect my app for not being a weak
保护我的应用程序不被弱者
I could actually have a qualified export
我实际上可以进行合格的出口
to Jackson yes yeah so so you know if
对杰克逊是的，所以你知道
you don't say week the default is that
你不说周默认是
the module is strong
模块很坚固
you then have to enumerate your exports
然后，您必须枚举您的出口
you can choose to have them being
你可以选择让他们
exported qualified to not just to
出口合格不仅限于
Jackson but to Jackson data bind in
杰克逊但对杰克逊的数据绑定
particular yeah yeah and the rules for
是的，特别是
reflection and regular access of these
反思和定期访问这些
signals exactly okay also they are
信号还好，他们也是
dominated by the exports that aren't on
以不出口的产品为主
this slide because they're they're
这张幻灯片，因为他们是他们
implicit but those providers to those
隐式但那些提供者
module or job we are we are hoping that
我们希望的模块或工作
framework developers like the Jackson
像Jackson一样的框架开发人员
developers will write module info dot
开发人员将编写模块信息点
Java files for their code and produce
Java文件及其代码和产生
modular jar files they're still jar
他们仍然是模块化的jar文件
files but they have this module info dot
文件，但它们具有此模块信息点
class file in them so that on jdk nine
它们中的类文件，以便在jdk九
the runtime knows to do the strong
运行时知道做强
encapsulation and the public it doesn't
封装和公众不
mean they will expose so is public
意味着他们将公开，所以公开
that's right so so if you look look at
没错，所以如果你看看
the crossed outlines so calm foster XML
交叉的轮廓使XML更加冷静
Jackson data bind DISA in pull that
杰克逊数据绑定DISA拉
package I'm pretty sure has public types
我很确定包有公共类型
in it those public types will only be
在这些公共类型中，只有
accessible within the data bind module
在数据绑定模块中可访问
which should be exposed but when when
应该暴露出来，但是什么时候
when another another provider they
当另一个提供商
mainly use this job but they define
主要使用这项工作，但他们定义
their own module then they expose this
他们自己的模块，然后他们公开
one when you use it even they are you
一个，当你使用它，即使他们是你
the same version but that you don't know
相同的版本，但您不知道
exactly what was it I'm confused sorry
到底是什么，我很抱歉
it's amazing in some ways it's always so
从某些方面来说，它总是如此令人惊奇
simple when you look at the artifacts
当您查看工件时很简单
but he did this and she did that well so
但他做到了，她做得很好
and so but don't don't reversions into
因此，但不要将其还原为
this you're saying this through his data
这是你通过他的数据说的
bind that has chosen to export a
选择导出的绑定
particular API right the author the
特定的API对作者
author of data bind is saying export the
数据绑定的作者说要导出
first four packages and then there's
前四个包，然后是
another one
另一个
etc etc you said you said another module
等等，你说你说另一个模块
another one when they define that
当他们定义另一个
Jackson annotation model infer file they
Jackson批注模型推断文件
say they expose this class okay so this
说他们公开这堂课好，所以这
was used by the define but another class
由定义使用，但另一个类
maybe my application I also use the
也许我的应用程序中我也使用了
Jackson a notation but I decided to use
杰克逊（Jackson）一种记法，但我决定使用
another the same version of annotation
另一个相同版本的注释
but the IP said I don't expose this
但IP表示我不公开
class then another one they use my
上课再用他们一个
application they also used a Jackson
他们还使用了杰克逊的应用程序
data ban when they look at the module
他们查看模块时的数据禁止
information they will see the same
他们将看到相同的信息
information because they use the same
信息，因为他们使用相同的
version then they learn to me pick one
版本，然后他们向我学习选一个
then then they don't expect the what the
那么他们就不会期望
real result I understand you're saying
真正的结果，我明白你在说
that the Jackson annotations module one
杰克逊注释模块之一
version exports package and another
版本导出包和另一个
version of Jackson annotation doesn't
版本的Jackson注释不
export the same package that's your
导出与您相同的包
scenario I think that's a little unusual
我认为这有点不寻常
that you can you could imagine it
你可以想象得到
happening but let's assume it happens
发生了，但让我们假设它发生了
Jackson whoever is picking the version
杰克逊（Jackson）选择版本的人
of Jackson data binds to go on the
杰克逊数据绑定继续
system
系统
because my app requires it also has to
因为我的应用要求它还必须
pick the version of jackson annotations
选择杰克逊注释的版本
that that record that very first
那首记录
requires clause will resolve against
require子句将针对
there's only one version of anything on
上只有一种版本
the system if there are two versions
系统是否有两个版本
jackson annotations pick one because i
杰克逊注解选了一个，因为我
think it's a good feature to have those
认为拥有这些是一个很好的功能
decided to expose which package you
决定公开你的包
can't do it on the classpath today you
今天你不能在类路径上做到这一点
can't do versions on the classpath if
如果不能在类路径上做版本
the next five questions are about
接下来的五个问题是关于
versions it's still gonna be pick one
版本仍然是一个
sorry thank you okay so you've shown how
抱歉，谢谢，好的，您已经展示了
to do top-down yeah when you're the
做自上而下的耶
application owner yes you know to do
应用程序所有者，是的，您知道吗
bottom-up yeah when you're a library
是的，当你是图书馆的时候
developer that has just Java modules
仅有Java模块的开发人员
dependency mm-hmm
依赖mm-hmm
what's the story if you in the middle so
你中间是怎么回事
you have library you'd like to move it
您有图书馆要移动
to be module but sadly some of your
成为模块，但不幸的是你的一些
dependencies are not yet modules should
依赖还不是模块应该
you do it or should you wait until the
您应该这样做还是应该等到
the graph underneath you is clean you
你下面的图很干净
should do it yes okay you should do it
应该去做，好吧，你应该去做
and you should document and when you do
你应该记录下来，什么时候做
it let me bring up take turbines so if
它让我带起涡轮机，如果
data binds required guava for example
数据绑定所需的番石榴
and guava is not yet an explicit module
番石榴还不是一个明确的模块
you are presumably testing your library
您大概正在测试您的库
against some version of guava you can
针对某些版本的番石榴，您可以
write requires guava in here I'll assume
写在这里我需要假设番石榴
it's it's not exposing guava types and
这是没有暴露番石榴类型和
signatures and you need to put in your
签名，您需要输入
documentation that please put guava
请放入番石榴的文件
download some version of guava and put
下载某些版本的番石榴并放入
it on the module path because you are
它在模块路径上，因为
being a good citizen but your this this
作为一个好公民，但是你这个
is the the issue of issues if if if if
问题的问题是如果
you wait to modularize
您等待模块化
then some other libraries correctly
然后其他一些库正确
tragedy of the Commons
下议院的悲剧
and it's important thing is is that
重要的是
libraries can actually migrate
库实际上可以迁移
independently that's that's really what
独立地那才是真正的
the first part of the person Park is
公园的第一部分是
there's just a small type in the in the
在里面只有一种
way you and the the modules end up being
您和模块最终的方式是
named so you need to pay attention I was
命名，所以你需要注意我
gonna say the next question that people
要说下一个问题
then ask is okay I'm data bind I'm a
然后问是好的我是数据绑定我是
good modular citizen who hopes to be
希望成为的好模范公民
linked into an image one day that would
链接到一天的图像
be nice but I require guava and guava is
很好，但我需要番石榴，番石榴是
working as an automatic module on my
作为我的自动模块
system in there for everyone's what
系统在那里每个人都
about when the vendor of that module of
关于何时该模块的供应商
that jar makes it into a modular jar
那个罐子变成一个模块化的罐子
when they declare a module and they
当他们声明一个模块，他们
decide to call it something else that
决定称它为其他东西
would be that would be impolite of them
那将是对他们的不礼貌
okay so in a way in a way the name that
好吧，以某种方式
your jar as today yes and the way you
像今天一样是你的罐子，你的方式
have automatic naming yes is be
有自动命名是
respected in the part of the public API
受到公共API的尊重
we should the second question is much
我们第二个问题应该很多
simpler so I missed the intro table so
比较简单，所以我错过了介绍表，所以
what I understand from here is the if
我从这里了解的是
you're just a regular you know
你只是普通人而已
application they will apply just depends
他们将适用的应用程序取决于
on libraries like Jackson and stuff so
在像杰克逊这样的图书馆上
then probably you should you should just
那也许你应该就应该
do the top down which it seems much less
自上而下，这似乎少得多
work mm-hm and it's just if your app is
工作毫米-毫米，这就像您的应用程序是
there you just set it Eclair it as a
在那里，您将其设置为Eclair
week so that's the contact but then if
周，所以联系，但是如果
you just do top down and get up and
你只要自上而下站起来
ready at least for your module I mean
至少为您的模块准备好了
your app to be modularized and that
您的应用程序将被模块化，
should be good enough to go it is very
应该足够好去了，这是非常
common to be able to download a jar from
能够从中下载jar的常见功能
the internet such as Jackson there like
像杰克逊这样的互联网
they might be JDK six five or six zero
他们可能是JDK六五或六零
class files in those jars put the jar on
这些罐子中的类文件将罐子放在
the module path it will very often work
它将经常工作的模块路径
as an automatic module
作为自动模块
which gives itself it's a name it
这就是它本身的名字
springs into existence so so that your
涌现出来，以便您
module info dot Java in your application
应用程序中的模块信息点Java
can require it that works surprisingly
可能会要求它出奇的效果
often and if it doesn't work don't call
通常，如果它不起作用，请不要打电话
us
我们
call the author of and I can tell you
给作者打电话，我可以告诉你
some of the reasons they are either they
原因是他们要么
are either accessing JDK internals which
要么正在访问JDK内部
is nothing there nothing to do with the
与...无关
modules it's not really the module
模块不是真正的模块
system it's not automatic modules that
系统不是自动模块
are the problem they're accessing some
是他们正在访问一些问题
internal thing and their jar won't work
内部的东西和他们的罐子不起作用
on the classpath either if they're not
如果不是，则在类路径上
accessing JDK internals you occasionally
偶尔访问您的JDK内部
find traditional jar files that contain
查找包含以下内容的传统jar文件
classes in the Java X annotation
Java X批注中的类
namespace in the Java X XML registry
Java X XML注册表中的名称空间
namespace and so on and so on
命名空间等等
they should not be including those
他们不应该包括那些
classes but they do and the module
类，但它们确实和模块
system at startup detects that there are
系统在启动时检测到
some package that has classes in the jdk
一些在jdk中具有类的包
image classes in this automatic module
此自动模块中的图像类
that's a bad thing something funny is
这是一件坏事，有趣的是
going on so the system will stop and if
进行下去，系统将停止，如果
that happens don't call us call the
发生这种情况不要打电话给我们
creator of that traditional jar to say
传统罐子的创造者说
why have you got Java SE types in your
为什么在您的Java SE类型中
random jar file that's never been a
从未有过的随机jar文件
supported thing can be it's actually
支持的东西可能是它实际上
relatively rare but when it happens you
相对罕见，但是一旦发生，您
are in trouble someone else has got you
遇到麻烦别人帮了你
in trouble thank you thank you UH one
有麻烦了谢谢谢谢你
more question yeah I think said we'll
是的，我想说我们会
have to wrap up them in this last
最后要把它们包起来
question outside of like smoothing over
像平滑以外的问题
some of the class path issues is there
有些班级问题
any other benefits that these modules
这些模块的任何其他好处
would give you are you developing is
会给你你正在发展
your jar an application jar that no one
您的jar是一个没有人的应用程序jar
calls or is is your code a library that
调用还是您的代码是一个库，
lots of other people have both okay
很多其他人都没事
how many jars are there in your
你有多少个罐子
application
应用
something there's probably maybe 30 50
大概有30 50
50 just in our application how do you
50刚在我们的应用程序中您如何
track the dependencies of code between
跟踪代码之间的依赖关系
classes in those jars is it a big ball
这些罐子里的课程是一个大球
of mud yeah that's what the JDK used to
是的，JDK曾经
look like the ability not only to
看起来不仅有能力
express the ability in a module to say
在模块中表达表达能力
not only what it depends on but also
不仅取决于它，而且
what its API is now there are some jars
它的API现在有一些罐子
at the very top of the graph that don't
在图的最上方
have an API there they got the main
有一个API，他们得到了主要
class but for everyone else there's an
课，但对于其他所有人
API that it is worth declaring
值得声明的API
explicitly you can declare these exports
明确地，您可以声明这些出口
are to everyone if you have a nest of
如果每个人都有巢穴
jar files you can export to your friends
您可以导出给朋友的jar文件
and what that means is you will never
那意味着你永远不会
again it's an investment you make once
再次，这是您一次的投资
and once you made it you will never
一旦成功，您将永远不会
backslide into why is he are you the
倒进他为什么是你的
business partner why is why is he
商业伙伴为什么是他为什么
calling this type in my package it was
在我的包裹中称这种类型是
meant to be internal protected as a
旨在作为一个内部保护
whole mess of access control complexity
混乱的访问控制复杂性
in order to share anything between
为了在之间共享任何东西
sometimes you want to share between
有时候你想分享
packages with public yeah you want to
与公众愿意的软件包
share with him other times you have
与他分享其他时间
types impact you you have a package that
类型会影响您的包装
you don't want to go outside a jar you
你不想去罐子外面
I'm pretty sure you at some point said
我很确定你在某个时候说
this package is just for other packages
这个包只适合其他包
in the same jar file that's it that's
在同一个jar文件中
what the module system gives you okay
模块系统能给您带来什么
thank you by the way on the ball of mud
谢谢，顺便说一句
we had a slide showing that in the intro
我们有一张幻灯片显示了介绍
talked earlier well the ball of mud is
刚才讲得好，泥球是
kind of that's a ball of mud
有点像泥泞的球
very symmetrical okay I think we're done
非常对称，好吧，我认为我们已经完成了
we're wrapping up thank you
我们结束了，谢谢